Register to The Charles Ives Papers
Yale University Music Library
- Correspondence, Series III; 13 boxes
  - Correspondence - Institutional, III.B
    - American Music Center (AMC) (Box 34, Folder 2)
      - American Music Center, 1941 Feb 14; 8 invoices (Box 34, Folder 2)
      - (Strauss, Florence), 1941 Feb 19, Mar 25; 2 typed letters signed (Box 34, Folder 2)
      - (White, Camilla), 1941 Oct 6, 1942 Feb 5; 2 typed letters signed (Box 34, Folder 2)
      - (Baskin, Dorothy), 1942 Jul 7; typed letter signed (Box 34, Folder 2)
      - Charles Ives to above, draft (Box 34, Folder 2)
      - (Kerr, Harrison), 1942 Aug 20; typed letter signed (Box 34, Folder 2)
      - Charles Ives to above, draft (Box 34, Folder 2)
      - (Kerr), 1942 Sep 22; autograph letter signed (Box 34, Folder 2)
      - (Kerr), 1942 Dec 3, Dec 7; 2 typed letters signed (Box 34, Folder 2)
      - (McMaster, Anne H.), 1943 Mar 10, May 25; typed letter signed (Box 34, Folder 2)
      - Charles Ives to above, draft (Box 34, Folder 2)
      - (Brandt, Shirley), 1943 Oct 28; typed letter signed (Box 34, Folder 2)
      - Charles Ives to above, draft 2 (Box 34, Folder 2)
      - (Brandt), 1943 Nov 18; typed letter signed (Box 34, Folder 2)
      - Charles Ives to above, draft (Box 34, Folder 2)
      - signed Charles Ives and Kerr, 1945 Oct 1; typed form (copy) (Box 34, Folder 2)
      - (Dower, Helen), 1945 Nov 15; typed (copy) (Box 34, Folder 2)
      - (Kerr), 1946 May 7; typed letter signed (Box 34, Folder 2)
      - (Dower), 1944 Apr 17, Apr 27; 2 typed letters signed (Box 34, Folder 2)
      - (Kerr), 1944 Apr 28; typed letter signed (Box 34, Folder 2)
      - (Brandt), 1944 Jul 27; typed letter signed (Box 34, Folder 2)
      - (Dower), 1944 Aug 3; typed letter signed (Box 34, Folder 2)
      - Charles Ives to above, draft (Box 34, Folder 2)
      - (Dower), 1944 Aug 23; typed letter signed (Box 34, Folder 2)
      - (Carter, Elliott), 1944 Oct 20; typed letter signed (Box 34, Folder 2)
      - (Dower), 1944 Nov 15; typed letter signed (Box 34, Folder 2)
      - Charles Ives to above, draft (Box 34, Folder 2)
      - (Kerr), 1945 May 15; typed letter signed (Box 34, Folder 2)
      - (Dower), 1945 Jun 11; typed letter signed (Box 34, Folder 2)
      - (Kerr), 1945 Sep 21; typed letter signed (Box 34, Folder 2)
      - American Music Center (AMC), draft (Box 34, Folder 2)
      - (Kerr), 1946 May 13; typed (copy) (Box 34, Folder 2)
      - (Kerr), 1946 May 27; typed letter signed (Box 34, Folder 2)
      - Charles Ives to above, draft (Box 34, Folder 2)
      - (Kerr), 1946 Jul 8; typed letter signed (Box 34, Folder 2)
      - Charles Ives to above, draft (Box 34, Folder 2)
      - (Dower), 1946 Aug 28; typed letter signed (Box 34, Folder 2)
      - American Music Center (AMC), 2 envelopes, one with Charles Ives memo (Box 34, Folder 2)
      - (Turner), 1947 Feb 24; typed letter signed (Box 34, Folder 2)
      - Charles Ives to above, draft (Box 34, Folder 2)
      - (Turner), *1947 Aug 6, Dec 8; 2 typed letters signed (Box 34, Folder 2)
      - (Pfutzner, Helen), 1947 Dec 19; *typed letter signed (Box 34, Folder 2)
      - (Turner), 1948 Feb 2; typed letter signed (Box 34, Folder 2)
      - 1948 Mar 15, envelope (Box 34, Folder 2)
      - (Kaye, Bess W.), 1948 Apr 7; 2 typed letters signed (Box 34, Folder 2)
      - (Green, Ray), 1949 Nov 30, 1950 Jan 9; 2 typed letters signed (Box 34, Folder 2)
      - Charles Ives for 1950 May 13, draft (Box 34, Folder 2)
      - (Green), 1950 May 25, 1951 Mar 5, 1950 Jul 10, 1953 May 25, Jul 1; 5 typed letters signed (Box 34, Folder 2)
      - Charles Ives, no date; draft 2 pp (Box 34, Folder 2)
      - Charles Ives to ?Kaye, draft (Box 34, Folder 2)
      - Charles Ives to Kaye, no date; typed letter signedft (Box 34, Folder 2)
      - Charles Ives to Kerr, no date; draft (Box 34, Folder 2)
      - Charles Ives to Kerr or Carter, no date; draft (Box 34, Folder 2)
      - Charles Ives to Turner, no date; draft (Box 34, Folder 2)
      - Charles Ives to Turner, no date; 9 draft (Box 34, Folder 2)
      - Charles Ives to Copland, no date; draft (Box 34, Folder 2)
      - Charles Ives to Kerr or Copland, draft (Box 34, Folder 2)
      - Harmony Twichell Ives to Dower, no date; *draft (Box 34, Folder 2)
    - American Music Rental Library (Box 34, Folder 3)
      - (Hull, Anne), 1940 Sep 23; typed letter signed (Box 34, Folder 3)
      - Charles Ives response, draft (Box 34, Folder 3)
      - (Strauss, Florine), 1940 Dec 4; typed letter signed (Box 34, Folder 3)
      - Charles Ives response, 1940 Dec 5; draft (Box 34, Folder 3)
      - (Strauss), 1940 Dec 6; typed letter signed (Box 34, Folder 3)
      - Charles Ives response, draft (Box 34, Folder 3)
      - (Hull), 1941 Feb 5; typed letter signed (Box 34, Folder 3)
      - Charles Ives response, draft (Box 34, Folder 3)
      - (Hull), 1941 May 7; typed letter signed (Box 34, Folder 3)
      - (Strauss), 1941 May 29; typed letter signed (Box 34, Folder 3)
        See also American Music Center
    - Charles Ives to American Red Cross, 1918 Jul 2; typed letter (Box 34, Folder 3)
      - 1918 Oct 4, (copy) and enc check Charles Ives $250 (Box 34, Folder 3)
    - to Harmony Twichell Ives American School of the Air (Herrmann, Bernard), no date; typed letter (copy) (Box 34, Folder 3)
    - American-Soviet Music Society, [1947?]; postcard (Box 34, Folder 3)
    - Annuaire International des Compositeurs, no date; typed (copy) (Box 34, Folder 3)
      - Charles Ives to above, no date; draft (Box 34, Folder 3)
    - Arizona State College (Holford, Ambrose), 1947 Dec 20; typed letter (copy) (Box 34, Folder 3)
      - Arizona State College (Holford, Ambrose), 1947 Dec 20; enc list (copy) and original (Box 34, Folder 3)
    - Arrow Music Press (Box 34, Folder 4)
      II.A Concord
      III.A/27/4/Copland, Cos Cob
      - (Kerr, Harrison), 1939 Jun 28; typed letter signed (Box 34, Folder 4)
      - Charles Ives, no date; draft (Box 34, Folder 4)
      - (Kerr), 1939 Jul 6; typed letter signed (Box 34, Folder 4)
      - Charles Ives, no date; draft (Box 34, Folder 4)
      - (Kerr), 1939 Jul 12; typed letter signed (Box 34, Folder 4)
      - Charles Ives, no date; draft (Box 34, Folder 4)
      - (Kerr), 1939 Aug 2; typed letter signed (Box 34, Folder 4)
      - (Brandt, Shirley), 1939 Oct 18; typed letter signed (Box 34, Folder 4)
      - Charles Ives, draft (Box 34, Folder 4)
      - (Kerr), 1939 Nov 1; typed letter signed (Box 34, Folder 4)
      - (Brandt), 1940 May 14; typed letter signed (Box 34, Folder 4)
      - Charles Ives, 1940 May 25; typed letter (copy) (Box 34, Folder 4)
      - (Brandt), 1940 May 31, Jun 20; 2 typed letters signed (Box 34, Folder 4)
      - (Brandt), 1940 Aug 19; autograph letter signed (Box 34, Folder 4)
      - Charles Ives, draft (Box 34, Folder 4)
      - (Brandt), 1940 Oct 17, Nov 1; 2 typed letters signed (Box 34, Folder 4)
      - Charles Ives, no date; draft (Box 34, Folder 4)
      - Charles Ives to Brandt, no date; draft (Box 34, Folder 4)
      - no date, draft (Box 34, Folder 4)
      - (Brandt), 1940 Nov 19; typed letter signed (Box 34, Folder 4)
      - Charles Ives, no date; draft (Box 34, Folder 4)
      - (Brandt), 1940 Nov 28; typed letter signed (Box 34, Folder 4)
      - Charles Ives, no date; draft (Box 34, Folder 4)
      - response 2, no date; draft (Box 34, Folder 4)
      - (Brandt), 1940 Dec 11; typed letter signed (Box 34, Folder 4)
      - Charles Ives, no date; draft (Box 34, Folder 4)
      - Arrow Music Press, draft 2 (Box 34, Folder 4)
      - to "K.H.", draft (Box 34, Folder 4)
      - (Kerr), 1940 Dec 19; typed letter signed (Box 34, Folder 4)
      - Charles Ives to Kerr, no date; 4 drafts (Box 34, Folder 4)
      - (Kerr), 1940 Dec 31; autograph letter signed (Box 34, Folder 4)
      - (Kerr), 1941 Jan 3; typed letter signed (Box 34, Folder 4)
      - (Kerr and Brandt), 1941 Jan 24; 2 typed letters signed (Box 34, Folder 4)
      - Charles Ives to Brandt, 1941 Jan 30; draft (Box 34, Folder 4)
      - (Marcus, Reba), 1941 Apr 16; typed letter signed (Box 34, Folder 4)
      - Charles Ives to Marcus, 2 drafts (Box 34, Folder 4)
      - (Marcus), 2 typed letters signed (Box 34, Folder 4)
      - (Marcus), 1941 May 3; 2 typed letters signed (Box 34, Folder 4)
      - Charles Ives, 1941 May 27; draft (Box 34, Folder 4)
      - (Williamson, Esther), 1941 Jul 15; typed letter signed (Box 34, Folder 4)
      - Charles Ives to above, draft (Box 34, Folder 4)
      - (Marcus), 1941 Sep 25; typed letter signed (Box 34, Folder 4)
      - (Kerr), 1942 Feb 25; typed letter signed (Box 34, Folder 4)
      - (Marcus), 1942 Mar 4; typed letter signed (Box 34, Folder 4)
      - Charles Ives to Kerr, no date; draft (Box 34, Folder 4)
      - (Marcus), 1942 May 16; typed letter signed (Box 34, Folder 4)
      - Charles Ives to Marcus, no date; draft (Box 34, Folder 4)
      - (Berman, Anne), 1942 Jun 11; typed letter signed (Box 34, Folder 4)
      - (Berman), 1942 Aug 10; typed letter signed (Box 34, Folder 4)
      - Charles Ives to Berman, no date; draft (Box 34, Folder 4)
      - (Berman), 1942 Sep 8; typed letter signed (Box 34, Folder 4)
      - (Kerr), 1942 Dec 30; typed letter signed (Box 34, Folder 4)
      - Charles Ives to Kerr, no date; draft (Box 34, Folder 4)
      - (Rosenblatt, May), 1943 Apr 8; typed letter signed (Box 34, Folder 4)
      - Charles Ives to above, no date; draft (Box 34, Folder 4)
      - (Kerr), 1943 Aug 13; typed letter signed (Box 34, Folder 4)
      - (Rosenblatt), 1943 Sep 1; typed letter signed (Box 34, Folder 4)
      - Charles Ives to above, no date; 2 drafts (Box 34, Folder 4)
      - (Kerr), 1944 Nov 22, Mar 22; 2 typed letters signed (Box 34, Folder 4)
      - (Turner, Godfrey), 1946 Oct 14, Nov 9, 1947 Apr 2; 3 typed letters signed (Box 34, Folder 4)
      - Charles Ives, no date; draft (Box 34, Folder 4)
      - (Turner), 1947 Jun 13, Jul 16; 2 typed letters signed (Box 34, Folder 4)
      - 1947 Sep 3, envelope (Box 34, Folder 4)
      - (Turner), 1947 Sep 9, Sep 25; 2 typed letters signed (Box 34, Folder 4)
      - Charles Ives to Turner, no date; 3 draft (Box 34, Folder 4)
      - (Turner), 1947 Oct 3, 1948 Jun 28; 2 typed letters signed (Box 34, Folder 4)
      - Charles Ives, no date [1949?]; draft (Box 34, Folder 4)
      - to Kerr, no date [1942?]; draft (Box 34, Folder 4)
      - to Williamson, no date [1941?]; draft (Box 34, Folder 4)
      - to Marcus, no date [1942?]; draft (Box 34, Folder 4)
      - to ?, no date; draft (Box 34, Folder 4)
      - to Turner, no date; draft (Box 34, Folder 4)
      - Charles Ives to Turner, no date; draft (Box 34, Folder 4)
      - no date, draft (Box 34, Folder 4)
      - [1948?], draft (Box 34, Folder 4)
      - (Copland), no date; 2 drafts (Box 34, Folder 4)
      - (Copland), 1950 May 23; autograph letter signed (Box 34, Folder 4)
      - 1952 Dec 31, 1955 Dec 31, 2 royalty statements (Box 34, Folder 4)
    - Associated Music Publishers
      See X.D/67/20
    - Atlas Musical Redaction, 1951 Feb 15; typed letter signed (Box 34, Folder 4)
    - Baldwin-Wallace (Poinar, George), 1947 Nov 6; typed letter signed (Box 34, Folder 5)
      - Baldwin-Wallace (Wolaver, John), 1948 Apr 22; autograph letter signed (Box 34, Folder 5)
      - Charles Ives to above, no date; draft (Box 34, Folder 5)
      - Harmony Twichell Ives to Wolaver, 1948 May 18; autograph letter signed (copy) (Box 34, Folder 5)
      - (Poinar), 1948 May 29; autograph letter signed (Box 34, Folder 5)
    - Berlin State Library (Altmann, W.), 1922 Sep 21; typed postcard signed (Box 34, Folder 5)
      - Charles Ives to above, 1922 Oct 15; autograph letter signed (Box 34, Folder 5)
    - Biographical Encyclopedia of the World, 1946 Oct 29; typed letter signed (Box 34, Folder 5)
      See also III.B/36/5/Who's Important in Music
    - Public Certificate Birchard, C.C. & Co., 1935 Jun 4; typed letter
      - Birchard, 1943 Nov 15, 1946 May 1, 1947 Apr 4, Dec 1, 1948 Mar 31; 5 bills (Box 34, Folder 5)
      - Charles Ives to Birchard, no date; 4 drafts (Box 34, Folder 5)
      - (Stevens, David), 1945 Apr 30; typed letter signed (Box 34, Folder 5)
      - see: Dark, Robert verso, 1945 Jul 28 (Box 34, Folder 5)
    - Bomart (Tietz, Margot J.), 1948 Nov 7; 2 typed letters signed
      - (List, Kurt), 1948 Nov 8 (Box 34, Folder 5)
      - Charles Ives to List, no date; 2 drafts (Box 34, Folder 5)
      - Charles Ives to Tietz, no date; draft (Box 34, Folder 5)
      - Bomart, 1949 Nov 11; typed letter signed (copy) (Box 34, Folder 5)
      - (Boelke, Walter R.), 1949 Dec; typed letter signed (Box 34, Folder 5)
    - Boston Symphony Orchestra
      See also III.A/29/9/Burk
      - (Burk, John W.), 1948 Feb 2; typed letter signed (Box 34, Folder 5)
      - Charles Ives to BSO, no date; draft (Box 34, Folder 5)
      - (Burk), 1948 Feb 13; typed letter signed (Box 34, Folder 5)
    - Bridgeport Herald (Beckwith, Ethel), 1947 May 13; typed letter signed (Box 34, Folder 5)
    - Bridgeport Post (Whelan, Anne), 1947 no date; typed letter signed (Box 34, Folder 5)
    - British Museum, London, acknowledgement signed
      - (Wilson, A.L.), no date (Box 34, Folder 5)
      - (King, A.H.), 1961 Sep 25; typed letter signed (Box 34, Folder 5)
      - 1935 Apr 12, receipt (Box 34, Folder 5)
    - Broude, Alexander
    - California Society of Composers
      See III.B/35/5/Native American Composers
    - UCLA (Petran, Laurence), 1946 Jun 15; typed letter signed (Box 34, Folder 6)
      - Charles Ives to above, no date; draft (Box 34, Folder 6)
      - (Petran), 1946 Nov 14; typed letter signed (Box 34, Folder 6)
    - Cape Cod Institution of Music
      See III.A/31/18/Shipman
    - Central Presbyterian Church (Avard, Mrs. G.W.), 1951 Mar 7, May 8; 2 typed letters signed (Box 34, Folder 6)
    - Central News, 1951 May 2; (enc) (Box 34, Folder 6)
    - The Charity Organization Society (Tousley, Clara M.), 1916 Mar 7; typed letter signed
      - 1916 Mar 25, receipt of check to above from Charles Ives (Box 34, Folder 6)
      - (Persons, W. Frank), 1916 Mar 23; typed letter signed (Box 34, Folder 6)
      - (Tousley), 1918 Apr 3; typed letter signed (copy) (Box 34, Folder 6)
      - (Rankin, A.H.), 1923 Oct 3; typed letter signed (Box 34, Folder 6)
    - Charles E. Merrill Co., Publishers (Merrill, Charles E.), 1929 Jan 17; typed letter signed (Box 34, Folder 6)
    - Chase National Bank, 1950 Jun 14; typed letter signed (Box 34, Folder 6)
    - Charles Ives to Chicago Music College, no date; draft (Box 34, Folder 6)
    - Chicago Plain Dealer
      See III.A/27/2/Bellamann
    - University of Chicago (Beals, Ralph), 1949 Mar 21; typed letter signed (Box 34, Folder 6)
    - City Club of New York (Childs, Richard), 1936 Jun 22 (Box 34, Folder 6)
    - Co-Art Recordings (Clement, Henry Lloyd), 1941 Dec 5; typed letter signed
      - Charles Ives to Clement, draft (Box 34, Folder 6)
      - (Clement), 1942 Feb 18; typed letter signed (Box 34, Folder 6)
      - Co-Art Turntable Vol.II, no. 2, Nov 1942; 3 publications (Box 34, Folder 6)
      - Vol.II, no. 3, Mar 1942 (Box 34, Folder 6)
      - Vol.II, no. 4, Apr 1942 (Box 34, Folder 6)
    - Columbia Graphophone Co. Ltd., bill
      - list by John Kirkpatrick, 1933 Jun 8 (Box 34, Folder 6)
      - 1933 Jun 8, cash receipt (Box 34, Folder 6)
      - 1933 Jun 13, bill (Box 34, Folder 6)
      - 1933 Jun 13, receipt (Box 34, Folder 6)
      - (Bigg, Robert), 1933 Jun 13; 2 typed letters signed (Box 34, Folder 6)
      - (Humphries, S.J.), 1933 Jun 26 (Box 34, Folder 6)
      - (Bigg), 1933 Jun 28; typed letter signed (Box 34, Folder 6)
      - John Kirkpatrick to Columbia Graphophone Co., 1962 Sep 18; typed letter (copy) (Box 34, Folder 6)
      - (Fowler, E.) to John Kirkpatrick, 1962 Oct 8; typed letter signed (Box 34, Folder 6)
    - Columbia Records Inc.
      See also II.A/29/3/Engel 1937 Jun 5
      - (Brown, Marianne), 1954 Jul 26 (Box 34, Folder 6)
      - Charles Ives to CBS (Mattfeld, J.), 1939 [?]; draft (Box 34, Folder 6)
      - response, 1939 Oct 20; typed letter signed (Box 34, Folder 6)
    - Columbia University (Moore, Douglas), 1946 Jan 31; typed letter signed
      - (Moore), 1946 Mar 22; typed letter (copy) (Box 34, Folder 6)
      - (Moore), 1946 May 13; typed letter signed (Box 34, Folder 6)
      - re Pulitzer, 1947 May 5 (Box 34, Folder 6)
      - verso reply Harmony Twichell Ives, 1947 May 7; telegram (Box 34, Folder 6)
      - (Ackerman, Carl W.), 1947 May 5; 2 typed letters signed (Box 34, Folder 6)
      - (Moore), 1947 May 20 (Box 34, Folder 6)
    - Committee of One Thousand, 1948 Mar 30; typed letter signed (Box 34, Folder 6)
      - (Brooks, Van Wyck), (enc) (Box 34, Folder 6)
    - Common Council for American Unity, 1944 May 16; postcard
      - (Lewis, Read), 1944 Dec 18; typed letter signed (Box 34, Folder 6)
      - (Lewis), 1946 Jun 5, 1947 May 2; 2 typed letters signed (Box 34, Folder 6)
    - Concert Hall Society, Inc. (Josefowitz, David), 1948 Aug 20; typed letter signed
      - Charles Ives to above, no date; 2 drafts (Box 34, Folder 6)
      - series announcement, 1948-1949; booklet (Box 34, Folder 6)
    - Connecticut State Federation of Music Clubs (Bolmer, Mrs. Clarence), 1930 Feb 10, 1937 May 19; 2 letters signed
      - Charles Ives to above, no date; 2 drafts (Box 34, Folder 6)
      - (Bolmer) to Edith Ives, 1937 Jun 5; card (Box 34, Folder 6)
    - Connecticut War Fund Campaign, no date; typed letter signed (Box 34, Folder 6)
      - Charles Ives to above, 1943 Nov 3; note (Box 34, Folder 6)
    - Charles Ives to Cos Cob Press, no date; draft (Box 34, Folder 6)
      - Cos Cob Press (Kalmus, Edwin F.), 1934 Jan 10; typed letter signed (Box 34, Folder 6)
    - Council for Democracy (Angell, Ernest), 1947 May 29; typed letter signed (Box 34, Folder 6)
    - Council Against Intolerance (Atkinson, Henry), 1947 Sep, 1948 Mar; 2 typed letters signed (Box 34, Folder 6)
    - The Crescendo Club (Sanders, Richard), 1940 Nov 18; typed letter signed (Box 34, Folder 6)
      other signatures: (Dahl, Tremblay, Zadir, Babitz, Weiss, others)
    - Charles Ives to Current Biography ?(Kothe[?], A.H.), no date; 2 drafts (Box 34, Folder 6)
    - Dahl, Ingolf
      See III.A/27/2/Babitz to Cowell
    - The Danbury Medical Society (DeKlyn, Ward B.), 1952 Oct 30; typed letter signed (Box 34, Folder 7)
    - Certificate of Publication for "Three Places in New England" Darewski Music Publishing Co., 1935 Apr 15 (Box 34, Folder 7)
    - Denison University
      See III.A/29/6/Eschman
    - University of Denver (Porter, R. Russell), 1948 Mar 15; telegram (Box 34, Folder 7)
      - Charles Ives to above, draft (Box 34, Folder 7)
    - Dickinson College
      See III.A/31/13/Schecter, Ralph
    - Ditson, Oliver Co. (Fisher, W.A.), 1921 Mar 8; typed letter signed (Box 34, Folder 7)
      See also III.A/29/7/Fisher
    - Durand fils (Charles Ives) under E. Fromont & Co. [?], no date; envelope (Box 34, Folder 7)
    - Emergency Committee of Atomic Scientists (Einstein, Albert), 1947 Aug 6; typed letter signed (Box 34, Folder 7)
    - Charles Ives to Equitable Life (Taylor, Wm.), 1922 Jul 1; typed letter signed (Box 34, Folder 7)
    - Etude Magazine (McCoy, Guy.), 1934 Jul 20; typed letter signed with Charles Ives memo (Box 34, Folder 7)
      - (McCoy) to Harmony Twichell Ives re Becker, 1956 Apr 2; typed letter signed (Box 34, Folder 7)
    - Fatherless Children of France (Namphiel [?] A.J.), 1918 Apr 8; typed letter signed (Box 34, Folder 7)
      - 1918 Apr 6, receipt (Box 34, Folder 7)
    - Fidelity-Phenix Fire Insurance Co. (Kennedy, Sidney R.), 1921 Mar 3; typed letter signed (Box 34, Folder 7)
    - Films (Leyda, Jay), no date; typed letter signed (Box 34, Folder 7)
      - Charles Ives to above, draft (Box 34, Folder 7)
    - The Florentine Bindery (Martin, Charles), 1934 May 15; typed letter signed (Box 34, Folder 7)
      See also III.A/29/Gershwin
    - Franco-American Musical Soc. (Dufour, Y.), 1925 Apr 3; typed letter signed (Box 34, Folder 7)
    - Friends of Democracy (Birkhead, L.M.), 1941 Jul 2, 1942 Dec 17; 2 typed letter signed
      - (Stout, Rex), 1944 Dec 28; typed letter signed (Box 34, Folder 7)
      - (Stout), 1947 Dec 9; typed letter signed (Box 34, Folder 7)
    - (Society of) Friends of Music Program with Charles Ives comment marginalia, no date (Box 34, Folder 7)
    - Friends of Music in the Library of Congress (Whitney, Myron W.), 1942 Jun 15; typed letter signed (Box 34, Folder 7)
    - Charles Ives to Fromont & Co., 1922 Jul 6; draft (Box 34, Folder 7)
      - Fromont & Co., 1922 Jul 6; typed letter (copy) (Box 34, Folder 7)
    - The Free Library of Philadelphia (Box 34, Folder 8)
      - (Price, F.H.), no date; typed letter signed (Box 34, Folder 8)
      - (Price), 1935 May 29; typed letter signed (Box 34, Folder 8)
      - (Price) with attached carbon of above typed letter signed, 1936 Feb 19; typed letter signed (Box 34, Folder 8)
      - (Price), 1936 Mar 19; typed letter signed (Box 34, Folder 8)
      - (Cohn, Arthur) with Charles Ives marginalia, 1942 Mar 25; typed letter signed (Box 34, Folder 8)
      - Charles Ives, 1942 Mar 31; typed letter (copy) (Box 34, Folder 8)
      - (Price), 1942 Apr 13; typed letter signed (Box 34, Folder 8)
      - (Cohn), 1942 Apr 14 to 1943 Feb 9; 7 typed letters signed (Box 34, Folder 8)
      - Charles Ives to above, no date; 2 drafts (Box 34, Folder 8)
      - (Price), 1944 Mar 23; typed letter signed (Box 34, Folder 8)
      - Charles Ives reply to above, draft (Box 34, Folder 8)
      - (Price), 1946 Mar 4; typed letter signed (Box 34, Folder 8)
      - Charles Ives, draft (Box 34, Folder 8)
      - list Harmony Twichell Ives, draft (Box 34, Folder 8)
      - (Price), 1946 Jun 11; typed letter signed (Box 34, Folder 8)
      - Charles Ives, draft (Box 34, Folder 8)
      - (Cohn), 1948 Feb 24; typed letter signed (Box 34, Folder 8)
      - Charles Ives response, draft (Box 34, Folder 8)
    - Galli Ormido (Galli, Ormido), 1938 Dec 10; typed postcard (Box 34, Folder 9)
    - Greenwich House Music School, 1937 Dec 18; autograph postcard
      - 1946 Jan 11, typed letter signed (Box 34, Folder 9)
      - Greenwich House Music School, 1937 Dec 18; brochure and card (Box 34, Folder 9)
      - (Powers, Maxwell), 1953 May 7; typed letter signed (Box 34, Folder 9)
    - Guggenheim
      III.A/27/12/Cohn
      III.A/32/7/Strang
    - Golden West Music Press
      - Charles Ives, no date; draft (Box 34, Folder 9)
      - Charles Ives to Langinger, Herman, 1933 Sep 15; autograph letter signed (copy) (Box 34, Folder 9)
      - (Langinger), 1932 Sep 25; typed letter signed (Box 34, Folder 9)
      - (Langinger) with Charles Ives note, 1933 Jan 26; typed letter signed (Box 34, Folder 9)
      - Charles Ives to Langinger, 10 drafts (Box 34, Folder 9)
      - (Langinger), 1935 Mar 27, Oct 4, 1937 Feb 11; 3 typed letters signed (Box 34, Folder 9)
    - Charles Ives to Hammond Vocal Arts, [?] Nov 5; draft (Box 34, Folder 9)
    - Harvard University Music Department (Hill, Edward Burlingame), 1921 Mar 15; typed letter signed (Box 34, Folder 9)
    - Homeyer & Co., Inc. (Knauber, H.), 1934 Feb 10; typed letter signed (Box 34, Folder 9)
    - Charles Ives to Hopkins Grammar School, no date; 2 drafts
      - (Farnham, Wm), 1950 Jul 10; 3 typed letters signed (Box 34, Folder 9)
      - (Barnett, Wm), 1935 Jun 6, May 25 (Box 34, Folder 9)
      - Hopkins School paper, 1953 Mar 27 (Box 34, Folder 9)
    - Ibbs & Tillett
      See III.A/30/8/Holmes
    - Independent Music Publishers, 1945 May 8; envelope with Charles Ives memo (Box 34, Folder 10)
      - Charles Ives to above (Abramson), no date; draft (Box 34, Folder 10)
    - Insurance Advocate, 1930 Mar 24; typed letter (Box 34, Folder 10)
    - Intercollegiate Broadcasting System, 1947 Oct 1; postcard (Box 34, Folder 10)